{
  "questions": {
    "question": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Which classmate sat with a Christmas background for far too long?",
        "answer": "Berat"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Which two classmates are siblings?",
        "answer": "Adam and Rickard"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Which classmate has puked in a police car?",
        "answer": "Joakim"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "Which classmate has a fluffy dog?",
        "answer": "Charlotte"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "How many classmates celebrate their birthday in September?",
        "answer": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Which classmate has read 'Sjörapporten' on SR P1?",
        "answer": "Fabiola"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "Who's having a great time abroad?",
        "answer": "Samuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "How large is the largest puzzle that Kicki has put together?",
        "answer": "5000"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Who has a cat with the same name as a classmate?",
        "answer": "Martina"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "What did the class get as fika in Gothemburg?",
        "answer":"Cinnamon rolls"
      },
      {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "Which two classmates lives in a city where there exists a serial pooper?",
        "answer": "Malek and Kicki"
      },
      {
        "id": "12",
        "question":"Who is the biggest Pokémon fan in the class?",
        "answer": "Maja"
      },
      {
        "id": "13",
        "question":"Who is the best photographer in the class?",
        "answer": "Lisa"
      },
      {
        "id": "14",
        "question":"Who has a degree in E-Com management?",
        "answer": "Philippa"
      },
      {
        "id": "15",
        "question":"Who serves the best drinks?",
        "answer": "Lisa"
      },
      {
        "id": "16",
        "question":"Who is the class sångfågel?",
        "answer": "Joakim"
      },
      {
        "id": "17",
        "question":"Who has lived on Malta for 2 years and in Australia for 3 years?",
        "answer": "Rickard" 
      }
    ]
  }
}